你有看过我们的银行对帐单了吗？没错吗？
Have you seen our bank statement? Can this be right?
就是嘛 天啊 从我小时候双层夹心饼上市之后…
I know. God, I haven't seen my savings take a hit like this...
我的存款就没这么少过
since I was a kid and they came up with Double Stuf Oreos.
- 我们的钱跑哪去了呢？ - 我不清楚他们做了什么…
- What happened to all of our money?     - Well, I'm not sure exactly what they did...
但是我倾向于责怪恩隆案
but I'm inclined to blame Enron.
我想是因为你在做实习工作
Well, I guess with you doing the internship...
我们花的比赚的还多
we're just spending more than we're bringing in.
是啊 或许我应该辞掉 然后找个有薪水的工作
Yeah, maybe I should quit and get a job that pays.
但是你终于找到你喜欢的工作了
But you're finally doing something that you love.
我是说 我不能要求你放弃
I mean, I can't ask you to give that up.
不过如果你喜欢做的事 是淘金 那就会好多了
Although it would be nice if the thing that you loved was, you know, finding gold.
我觉得我们太小题大作了
You know what? I think we're making too big a deal out of this.
好 我们这个月会比较紧
Okay? So we pay our bills late this month.
下个月我们就节省一些开销
Maybe next month, we cut back on a few things.
而且或许我们可以改变一下 到乔伊家的冰箱找食物
And maybe we start eating out of Joey's refrigerator for a change.
你是厨师 你可以用苏打粉跟啤酒做出什么呢？
You're a chef. What can you make out of baking soda and beer?
最糟糕的情况下 我们只好跟我父母借钱
All right. Worst-case scenario is, we borrow some money from my parents.
不行 我们不借钱
No, we're not borrowing money.
- 为什么不行？ - 因为我们不那样做 我们是宾家的人
- Why not?     - Because we don't do that. We are Bings.
我爸有教过我
If there's one thing my father taught me, it was...
在进入撞球间时一定要先敲门
well, to always knock before going into the pool house.
还有 永远都不要借钱
But the other thing was, never borrow money.
我不知道你是如此有荣誉感
Wow, I had no idea you had this much pride.
没错 我就是 我是你男人
That's right, I do. I am your man.
我会让我们度过难关的
And I'm gonna get us through this situation...
就算要你加倍努力工作也是
even if it means you working twice as hard.
- 我要回去了   - 为什么？
- I'm gonna go.     - Why?
我有好几天没有回家了 而且我需要多拿几件衣服
I haven't been home in a couple days and I need to get more clothes.
你不用回去 我有衣服可以给你穿
You don't have to go. I have something that'll fit you.
我穿女生的紧身衣是为了好玩
I put that tube top on as a joke.
- 我想要你留下来   - 我也想要留下来
- I want you to stay.     - I want to stay too.
但是我已经不能再穿这几件内裤了
But I've got as much use out of these boxers as I can.
- 为什么不反过来再穿呢？ - 已经反过了
- Why don't you turn them inside...     - Done it.
- 我几个小时之后就回来   - 好吧 我会想你的
- I'll be back in a couple of hours.     - All right. I'll miss you.
我也是
Me too.
你知道吗？我刚惊觉到一件事 我不想要回家
You know what? I just realized something. I don't want to go home.
- 太好了 好的 我去拿紧身衣   - 不 我的意思是…
- Great! Okay, I'll go get the tube top.     - No, no, what I mean is...
- 我不喜欢回去自己的公寓   - 嗯
- I hate going back to my apartment now.     - Mm-hm.
一方面是因为我住在一间脏乱的小房间里面
Partly because I live above a known crack den...
但是 主要是因为我回去的时候 我真的好想你
but, you know, mostly because when I'm there, I really miss you.
所以…
So...
你想不想搬一起住呢？
do you want to move in together?
哇 麦克汉尼根
Wow, Mike Hannigan...
你倒是挺清楚要如何 让女生说"好"
you sure know how to make a girl say "Hell, yeah."
- 那我们要这样做吗？ - 好啊 就这样做 我们- 起住
- So we're doing it?     - Yeah, let's do it. Let's live together.
我们真的要同居吗？
Wow. We're really gonna move in together?
是啊
Yeah.
我一直都想要跟男生同居
I've always wanted to live with a guy.
袜子捡起来 马桶坐垫放下来
Pick up your socks. Put down the toilet seat.
不 我再也不跟你做爱了
No, we are not having sex anymore.
一定会很好玩
It's gonna be fun.
- 嘿 乔伊   - 嘿
- Hey, JOEY-     - Hey.
听着 我需要你保证 我接下来要问你的事…
Listen, I need to know that what I'm about to ask you...
不会被钱德知道
will never get back to Chandler.
如果说我没有想过那件事 我就是在说谎
I'd be lying if I said I hadn't thought about it myself.
但是钱德是我最好的朋友 那是不对的
But Chandler is my best friend. It would be wrong.
感觉不错 却是不对的
Good, but wrong.
好的 首先 感觉会是棒透了
Okay, first of all, it would be great.
但那不是我想跟你说的事 我需要跟你借钱
But that's not what I'm here to talk to you about. I need to borrow money.
喔 我不知道 摩妮卡 你知道的
Oh, I don't know, Monica. You know...
借钱给朋友不是什么好事
lending friends money is always a mistake.
- 但钱德借过你钱   - 而他也会告诉你那不是什么好事
- But Chandler lent you money.     - And he would tell you it was a mistake.
别这样 我只是… 我需要付房租跟一些帐单
Come on, I just... I need it for some rent and some other bills.
多少钱呢？
Oh, well... Well, how much?
- 两千块   - 两千块？
- Two thousand dollars?     - Two thousand dollars?
你以为我是谁？肥皂剧明星吗？
What do you think I am, a soap-opera star?
- 是啊   - 没错 我就是
- Yeah.     - That's right, I am.
- 嗨 你们好   - 嘿
- Hi, you guys.     - Hey.
- 袋子里面是什么？ - 你们都知道艾玛已经开始会爬了
- What's in the bag?     - You know how Emma started crawling?
我发现这地方对婴儿而言 是很不安全的
I realized that this place is very unsafe for a baby...
所以我去店里买了一些东西 来让公寓更适合婴儿活动
so I went to the store and I got some stuff to baby-proof the apartment.
喔 天啊 适合婴儿
Oh, God, baby-proofing.
有什么了不起的呢？我小的时候 常常都…
Why is it such a big deal now? You know, when I was a kid, it was like:
"哇 乔伊跌下楼梯了"
"Whoops, Joey fell down the stairs."
或是"哇 乔伊又电到自己了"
Or, "Whoops, Joey electrocuted himself again."
你要找人帮忙安装这些东西吗？
Anyway, um, are you going to get a handyman to install this stuff?
- 不 我自己来就行了   - 哈 哈
- No, I was just gonna do it myself.     - Ha, ha.
- 你要自己来？ - 是啊 不行吗？
- You're gonna do it'?     - Yeah. Why?
- 你觉得女人不可能自己做吗？ - 女人可以 你不行
- You don't think a woman can do this?     - Women can. You can't.
摩妮卡 可以请你告诉乔伊 他是猪吗？
Monica, will you please tell Joey that he is a pig.
- 你是猪 而你不会做   - 什么？
- You're a pig. And you can't do this.     - What?
别这样 我自己找到五金店的
What? Come on, I found the hardware store all by myself.
那间店就在街尾
The hardware store's right down the street.
街尾就有一间五金店吗？
There is a hardware store right down the street?
嘿 各位 我们有好消息要宣布
Hey, you guys? Okay, we've got great news.
- 菲比跟我要一起同居了   - 恭喜了
- Phoebe and I are moving in together.     - Congratulations.
我知道 好兴奋 我从来都没有跟男生同居过
I know, it's so exciting. You know, I've never lived with a guy before.
嗯 那就像跟女生一起住一样 只是他们不会偷用你的化妆品
Well, it's just like living with a girl, only they don't steal your makeup.
除非他们是在玩 "我妹妹就是长这样"
Unless they're playing "This ls What My Sister Would Look Like."
是啊 她不太可爱
Yeah, she's not so cute.
- 我要上洗手间   - 上完把马桶坐垫放下来
- I'm gonna go to the bathroom.     - Well, you put down the toilet seat.
是的 亲爱的
Yes, dear.
- 那是你们在玩的游戏吗？ - 是啊 我们在模仿你们俩个
- Is that a bit you guys do?     - Uh-huh. We're playing you two.
我们没有那样 告诉她我们没有
We don't do that. Tell her we don't do that.
我们有 亲爱的
Yes, dear.
不敢相信你们要同居了 我真替你们高兴
I can't believe you're moving in together. That's gre... I'm happy for you guys.
- 我听到婚礼进行曲了   - 摩妮卡 别急好吗？
- I hear wedding bells.     - Monica, slow down, okay?
我只是很兴奋要跟他一起住而已
I'm just excited to be living with him.
你知道的 我是说 我不知道…
You know, I mean, I don't know...
我能预见有天跟麦克结婚吗？是的 当然
can I see someday being married to Mike? Sure. Yeah.
我可以想像自己 穿着婚纱走在红毯上
You know, I could picture myself walking down the aisle...
婚纱以很明显 但高雅的方式 集中突出我的胸部
in a wedding dress that highlights my breasts in an obvious yet classy way.
但问我想不想要在康乃狄克州 有好学区的房子…
But do I want that house in Connecticut, you know, near the good schools...
让麦克跟我送我们的 小苏菲跟小麦克去上学？
where Mike and I could send little Sophie and Mike Jr.?
喔 我的天 我好想
Oh, my God, I do.
菲比 我不晓得你是这么传统的人
Phoebe, I had no idea you were so conventional.
我想我是的
I know. I guess I am.
我的天 开着富豪汽车 大包小包的 我要变成足球妈妈了
Oh, my God, load up the Volvo, I want to be a soccer mom.
- 你准备好要走了吗？ - 当然好罗 新室友
- You ready to go?     - Yeah, you bet, roomie.
你是说"新郎"吧
Don't you mean "groomie"?
- 你在说什么？ - 拜托
- What are you talking about?     - Please.
我们都还没一起住
These guys. We haven't even moved in yet...
而他们就要我们选结婚礼物了
and they have us picking out china patterns.
结婚礼物
China patterns!
这很容易的 "你不行…"
This is easy. "Can't do this..."
哇 还真的咧 就是不行
Wow, seriously. Can't do this.
(中央咖啡厅)
- 嘿 乔伊   - 嘿
- Hey, Joe.     - Hey.
听着 我需要你帮个忙 而且不能跟摩妮卡说
Listen, um, I need to ask you a favor,and we can't tell Monica anything about it.
- 我以为你们之间没有秘密   - 表面上是那样没错
- I thought you guys didn't have secrets.   - That will remain the official party line.
摩妮卡跟我有一点点经济上的问题
Look, Monica and I are having a little financial trouble.
- 是啊 我知道   - 什么？你知道是什么意思？
- Yeah, I know.     - What? What do you mean, you "know"?
嗯
Uh...
我猜的 你知道的
I just figured it out, you know?
我是说 你没有工作 而且现在经济又很萧条
I mean, you're not working and, uh, the economy is bad.
喔 对
Oh, right.
这是我反应最快的一次了
That is the fastest I have ever thought.
反正…
Anyway, uh...
我需要跟你借点钱
I need to borrow some money.
当然罗 多少钱？两千块吗？
Oh, sure. Yeah, how much? Two thousand dollars?
是的 正是两千块 你是怎么知道的？
Yes, $2000 exactly. How did you know that?
我知道你之前赚多少钱 而且我也知道你们的房租
Uh, well, I know how much you used to make...and I know how much your rent is.
喔 好的
Oh, okay.
我真是天才
I am on fire.
听着 你真好 你…
Listen, this is really nice.
你开一张两千块的支票给摩妮卡？
Did you write a check to Monica for $2000?
摩妮卡跟你借钱？
Did Monica borrow money from you?
- 好像是   - 我不敢相信她竟然这样做
- Uh, kind of.     - I can't believe her.
她有跟你说我们有经济问题吗？
Did she tell you we were having money problems?
不 不是为了你们的经济问题
No, no, no. It wasn't because of your money problems.
是她自己的东西
It was for something for her.
什么？
What?
很和人的东西
Something personal.
她要花两千块还不能告诉我的 是什么东西？
What would she get for $2000 that she wouldn't tell me about?
不好意思
Excuse me.
隆胸术
Boob job.
她根本不需要隆乳手术 这真是疯狂
I don't want her to get a boob job. That's crazy.
不算太疯狂 好吗？
Well, it's not that crazy, okay?
把咪咪变小才叫做疯狂
Making them smaller, that would be crazy.
嘿 我想要问你关于 摩妮卡的"新郎"笑话
Oh, hey, I wanted to ask you about Monica's little "groomie" joke.
我想大家会笑 是因为她在玩"新室友"这个词
Well, I think the reason people laughed is that it's a play on the word "roomie."
不
No...
我听得懂这个笑话 真是高深啊
I get the joke. Sophisticated as it was.
不 我要说的是…
No, the thing I want to say is...
或许我们之前就应该先谈过
Maybe we should've talked about this before.
我们住在一起这件事 你应该没有期望我会求婚吧
Us living together, you're not expecting a proposal, right?
- 喔 不 不   - 点也没有   - 好的
- Oh, no, no. Not at all.     - Okay.
我们才刚搬进来一起住 再看看吧
We're just moving in right now. We'll see where it goes.
对 这就是个问题 对我而言 这已经是我的极限了
Yeah, well, that's the thing. For me, it's as far as it can ever go.
- 你是什么意思？ - 听着 菲比 我…
- What do you mean?     - Look, Phoebe, I...
我非常爱你 但我不想再结婚了
I love you very much. But I never want to get married again.
喔
Oh.
- 哇   - 只是我的第- 次婚姻太…
- Wow.     - It's just, my first marriage was...
太糟糕了 我已经对婚姻失去信心了
you know, such a disaster that I kind of lost faith in the whole idea.
- 有那么糟吗？ - 有一次 到最后…
- Mm-hm. Was it really that bad?     - At one point, near the end...
- 她故意便便在我的…   - 喔 那真糟
- she deliberately defecated on my...     - Okay, well, that's bad. Yeah.
但是你不认为换梱人会不一样吗？
But don't you think it might be different with someone else? Perhaps...
或许是一个会在厕所便便的金发女郎？
a blond who always uses the toilet?
除了有一次是便在海里
Except for once in the ocean.
听着 不是我要娶谁的问题
Look, it's not about who I would marry.
我本来也确定我第一次的婚姻 会维持永远 但我错了
I was certain the first time I got married it would last forever. I was wrong.
- 但是 只是…   - 菲比 不是你的原因
- But, it just...     - Look, Phoebe, it's not about you.
我只是再也不想结婚了
I just never want to get married again.
- 哈   - 我很抱歉
- Ah.     - I'm sorry.
你可以接受吗？如果不行的话 或许我们一起住不是个好主意
Are you okay with that? If not, maybe us moving in together isn't the best idea.
可以 喔 我当然也不希望结婚
No. Oh, I definitely don't want to get married.
我只想确定你也不想要
No, I just wanted to make sure you didn't want to, too.
因为如果我们住在一起 然后你开始改变心意…
Because, you know, if we move in and you start changing your mind...
我们就有麻烦了 先生
there is gonna be hell to pay, mister.
- 相信我 我永远不…   - 好的 我知道了
- Trust me. I will never...     - Yeah, I get that. Yeah.
嗨 最后你决定请人来帮忙了？
Hi. So you gave in and decided to call someone?
是啊 我不知道我在想什么 我连筷子都不会用
Yeah. I don't know who I was kidding. I can barely use chopsticks.
- 都装好了   - 喔 真的很谢谢你
- You're all set.     - Oh, thank you so much.
等等 你忘了你的…
Wait. You forgot your, um...
玩具
Your game.
谢谢你
Thank you.
嘿 瑞秋 我身材完美的老婆在这里
Hey, Rach. There she is, my perfectly proportioned wife.
别看我 我从来没有听懂过他的笑话
Don't look at me. I never get his jokes.
- 谢谢你   - 不 不 别谢我
- Thank you?     - No, no. Don't thank me.
谢谢你 你知道我不会想要 改变你任何一点吗？
Thank you. Do you know there is not one thing that I would change about you?
一点也没有 而且特别是…
Not one single thing. And definitely not...
那两点
two single things.
好的 你真的很怪 你想上床吗？
Okay, you're being weird. Do you want sex...
还是做了什么错事？
or did you do something bad?
不 不 不 我就是爱你这模样 我爱你的…
No. No. No. I just love the way you look. I am warm...
身材
for your form.
好的 你知道传统上都是说 "你看起来很好"吧？
Okay, um, you know the old classics like, you know, "You look nice"?
这句话还是适用
They're still okay.
但是"你看起来很好"可能只是代表 "你的脸蛋看起来很好"
But "you look nice" could mean that I'm saying, "Your face looks nice."
我想要赞美你的身体
I want to compliment your body.
我是说 我一点都不想改变它
I mean, I wouldn't change it at all.
而且更详细地说 就是 我不想要加大任何东西
And more specifically, I wouldn't want anything to get any bigger.
- 好的   - 我是说…
- Okay.     - I mean...
你也不会想要我身体的某部分加大 不是吗？
you wouldn't want any part of me to get any bigger, would you?
不用回答
Don't answer that.
我还以为那老兄不可能更怪了
Just when you thought that dude couldn't get any weirder.
你觉得他为何会担心我会变大？
I know. Why do you think he was so worried about me getting bigger?
我不知道 那是怎么回事呢？
I don't know. I mean, what brought that on'?
我的天 你知道吗？我们正努力要怀孕…
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. You know what? We're trying to get pregnant...
所以他可能很怕我的身材会变形
so he's probably starting to freak out that my body's gonna change.
- 你认为是这样吗？ - 你也看到了
- You think that's what it is?     - You heard him.
"不要变大 你很完美了 不要再变大了"
"No bigger. You're perfect. Just don't get any bigger."
天啊 他听起来就像是 我高中的摔跤教练
My God, he sounded just like my high-school wrestling coach.
- 我必须要跟钱德谈谈   - 是啊 如果你不去 我会去
- I'm gonna have to talk to Chandler.     - Yeah. If you don't, I will.
当然你的身材会变形 你的胸部会变大
Of course your body's gonna change. Your breasts are gonna get bigger...
你的屁股会变大
your ass is gonna get bigger...
你会膀胱无力
you're gonna lose bladder control.
我的天 真是奇妙的时期啊
God, it's just such a magical time.
- 嗨   - 嘿
- Hi.     - Hey.
听着 我想要请教你关于婚姻的事
Listen, I wanted to ask you something about marriage.
现在你跑来找我 是要取笑我吗？
Now you're seeking me out to make jokes?
我们出去在一起的时候被取笑 我可以理解 但是跑到我家来…
I mean, I can see if we're all hanging out, but to come to my home...
不 我真的想知道你的意见
No, I really want to know how you feel about it.
- 为什么？ - 麦克永远不想要结婚
- Why?     - Mike doesn't ever want to get married.
- 永远吗？ - 永远
- Never?     - Never.
哇 你还要跟他同居吗？
Wow. Are you still gonna move in with him?
我想啊 但是我要你告诉我 结婚真的不算什么
I want to, but I wanted you to tell me that marriage really isn't that big a deal.
没结婚也不会后悔 婚姻烂毙了
You know, that I won't be missing out on anything. That marriage stinks.
是啊 婚姻烂毙了
Yeah, marriage stinks.
我是说 如果你想看到男人变肥 女人不再除毛…
I mean, if you want to see a man gain weight and a woman stop shaving...
就叫他们结婚吧
get them married.
- 那不是你真正的感觉 对吧   - 不是 我很抱歉
- That's not how you really feel, is it?     - No, I'm sorry.
我知道那不是你想听的话 但是我没有办法说谎
Look, I know it's not what you want to hear, but I can't help it.
我喜欢结婚
I love marriage.
真的吗？你这个"离婚专家"？
Seriously, you? Divorce-0?
如果你要帮我取绰号我比较喜欢 "罗斯 离婚王" 听来较酷
If you have to call me a name, I'd prefer "Ross, the Divorcer." It's just cooler.
听着 我知道我的婚姻并没有成功
Look, look, I know my marriages didn't exactly work out...
但我喜欢对另一个人做那种程度的承诺
but, you know, I loved being that committed to another person.
在卡萝变成女同性恋之前 我们度过许多快乐的时光
And Carol and I had some good times before she became a lesbian.
之后还有一次
And once afterward.
反正 很抱歉
Anyway, I'm sorry.
没关系 这是你的真实感受
Ugh. It's okay. That's how you feel.
但是 别这样 住在一起也很棒阿
But, come on, I mean, living together will be great.
我是说你们会很快乐的 而且你爱麦克啊
I mean, you guys have so much fun. And you love Mike.
- 我是很爱麦克   - 是啊 不是吗？
- I do love Mike.     - Yeah, see?
而且你之前很期待同居的
And you were so excited about moving in together before...
而且你知道吗？期待是对的 这是很大的一步
and you know what? You should be. It's a big deal.
是啊 我想你说的对
Yeah, I guess you're right.
是啊 谢谢 真有帮助 谢谢
Yeah, thanks. This helped. Thanks.
离婚王拯救众生
The Divorcer to the rescue.
- 并没有比较酷   - 我听到了
- It's not cooler.     - Yeah, I just heard it.
喔
Oh.
瑞秋？
Rash?
瑞秋
Rachel?
所以我想做什么都不行吗？
So I can't do anything I like?
嘿 瑞秋
Hey, Rach.
完美 什么都不必改变 完美无缺
Ah, perfection. Wouldn't change a thing. Not a thing.
- 亲爱的   - 怎样？
- Honey?     - Yeah?
关于那件事
About that.
- 我会变的   - 是的 但是亲爱的 你不需要
- Um, I'm going to change.     - Yes, but, honey, you don't have to.
我会变得大一点
I'm gonna get bigger.
亲爱的 我…
Honey, I...
我喜欢你胸部现在的样子
I love your breasts the way they are.
大男人
Ugh. Fascist.
我的胸部会变大的 不管你喜不喜欢
Well, my breasts are gonna get bigger whether you like it or not.
而且不只是我的胸部 我的屁股也会变大
And it's not just my breasts. My ass is gonna get bigger too.
你的屁股？
Your ass?
而且如果她的手脚也变大 别太惊讶
And don't be surprised if her hands and her feet get bigger too.
- 他们也会吗？ - 这是整套的
- They do that?     - It's kind of a package deal.
天啊 为什么？为什么你要对自己做这种事呢？
God, why? Why would you want to do that to yourself?
我以为这是我们俩都想要的
I thought it was something that we both wanted.
如果这对你那么重要 关于胸部 我或许可以释怀
If it means that much to you,I may be able to get on board with the big boobs...
但是大屁股还有大脚丫？
but the giant ass and the big clown feet?
喔 天啊 钱德
Oh, my God, Chandler.
如果你连这个都受不了 那你到了医院要怎么办…
If you can't handle this, what are you gonna be like in the hospital...
加上流血和尖叫声 还有那个 从她身体挤出来的小小人？
with the blood and screaming and the little person that's shooting out of her?
什么？
What?
乔伊 你为什么要跟钱德说 摩妮卡要去做隆乳手术呢？
Joey, why did you tell Chandler that Monica was getting a boob job?
因为她是要啊
Because she is.
- 乔伊 钱德知道我跟你借钱了   - 为了要做隆乳手术
- Chandler knows I borrowed the money.     - Mm-hm. For your boob job.
- 乔伊   - 结束了
- Joe...     - It's over.
好了 所以我借出了四千块 结果没有人的胸部会变大？
Okay, so I'm out $4000 and nobody's boobs are getting any bigger?
嘿 嘿 你们觉得这样如何呢？"罗斯 离婚强棒"
Hey. Hey, what do you guys think about this: Ross, the Divorce Force.
- 比较好   - 是吗？
- Better.     - Yeah?
非常酷
Very cool.
嘿 菲比 我真的很高兴那天你过来找我谈
Hey, Pheebs? You know,I'm really glad you came to talk to me the other day...
- 希望我有帮上忙   - 是啊 你帮忙很大
- and I hope I was a little helpful.     - Oh, yeah, you were helpful.
- 是啊 很谢谢你   - 很好 很好
- Yeah. No, thank you.     - Good. Good.
因为我越想越觉得…
Because the more I thought about it, the more I realized...
婚姻对你而言 不见得是必经之路
I don't think marriage is necessarily the right path for you.
你是什么意思？
What do you mean?
我知道那天在咖啡屋的时候…
I know the other day in the coffeehouse...
你很沉醉于当足球妈妈什么的
you were all caught up in the whole soccer-mom thing...
但是那是真的你吗？你可以想像自己开着富豪汽车吗？
but is that really you? I mean, can you honestly picture yourself in a Volvo?
富豪汽车是太有棱有角了
They are awfully boxy.
我是说 婚姻对你是很无趣的 我是说 那太中规中矩了
I mean, I don't know, you'd be so bored with marriage. I mean, it's so normal.
是啊
Uh-huh. Yeah.
嘿 需要帮忙吗？
Hey, can I help?
我们爬了四层楼 好不容易通过狭窄的通道
Well, we climbed up four flights of stairs, maneuvered a narrow hallway...
再躲过一只狂犬病斗牛狗 但是最后这三英里路才是最崎岖的
dodged a rabid pit bull.But these last three feet are where it gets really tricky.
有时候你的话真伤人
You know, sometimes your words, they hurt.
嘿 你们要把这个放哪呢？
Hey, where do you guys want this?
是啊 快点 因为真的很重
Yeah, seriously, because this is really heavy.
不是对我 因为我只是假装扶着 但是他们几个真的快被重死了
I mean, not for me, because I'm only pretending to hold it, but for these guys.
最后再问你一次结婚的事 没有再思考的空间吗？一点都没有？
Just one last time on the marriage thing. There's no wiggle room? None at all?
没有 但你也不想结婚 不是吗？
No, but you don't want to get married either, right?
没错
Right.
只是 我是真的很想结婚
Except that I do want to get married.
不能在楼下卸货前先谈这个吗？
Couldn't have had this conversation down at the truck, huh?
什么？你想要结婚？
What? You want to get married?
总有一天
Someday.
还有…疝气
And hernia.
我从未有过正常的生活 而我也从没有觉得失去过什么
I haven't had a normal life.And I never felt like I was missing out on anything.
但是总觉得好像 该轮到我拥有正常的东西了
But it feels like now it's my turn to have some of the regular stuff.
如果想结婚 你为什么不早说呢？
If you wanted to get married, why didn't you say something before?
我之前不确定我有多想要
Because I didn't know how much I wanted it.
而且我爱你 我想要跟你一起住
And I love you, and I wanted to live with you.
我也想跟你一起住 我们就这样做吧
I wanna live with you too. I mean, let's do that.
但是我不觉得我可以
But I don't think I can.
当我不清楚未来时 我们是可以一起住
It was okay to move in when I didn't know what was gonna happen.
但在知道将来什么事都不会发生之后 我就没办法了
But I can't move in knowing nothing is ever gonna happen.
我们可以至少先试试同居吧？你或许会改变对婚姻的想法
Can we at least try living together? You might change your mind about marriage.
你会改变你的想法吗？
Are you gonna change yours?
不会
No.
我也不会
Me neither.
我想我需要跟想法一样的人在一起
Um, I think I need to be with someone who wants what I want.
但是我不想要结束
But I don't want this to end.
我也不想要结束
No, I don't want it to end either.
我不敢相信就要这样结束了
I can't believe this is gonna end.
我会把我的东西打包好
I guess I'll have my stuff picked up.
好的
Yeah. Okay.
好的 那么…
Okay, so, uh...
再见
Good bye.
- 再见 麦克   - 拜 麦克
- Take it easy, Mike.     - Bye, Mike. See you later, Mike.
我很难过 菲比
I'm so sorry, Pheebs.
我们都很难过
We're all sorry.
往好处想
Look on the bright side.
至少你不用跟那张丑椅子在一起
I mean, at least you won't have to live with this ugly chair.
那早就在这里了 对不对？
That was here already, huh?
我爱你
I love you.
我办到了 我办到了
I did it! I did it! Ha, ha!
太好了
All right.
最好拿多一点
I'd better take all I can carry.
谁知道下次能不能打得住呢？
Who knows when I'll be able to get in here again, huh?